KEVIN KIM

CONSTRUCTIVE SELF-MOTIVATED FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Skillful and passionate full-stack developer specializing in web development applications. Completed and working on different projects involving frontend, back-end and mobile development environments. Excellent team player who brings synergy with situational leadership into challenges with attentive communication skills

HIGHLIGHT

- Strong knowledge in Java, C, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, GraphQL and Linux
- Educational background majored in Software Development from South Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT)
- Proficient in MS Office Software including Word, Excel, PowerPoint with typing speed 70wpm
- 3+ years of experience in organizing projects and supervising team members

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Manager SK Solutions Calgary/Edmonton

Nov 2013 - Apr 2015, Apr 2017 - Sep 2019

- Increased about 200% of the profit with the high-quality work in Labor Market Impact Assessment; completed +100 applications every year which is about 10% of the total approval in the entire Alberta region
- Saved by 10% of the time for intake/submission application; rebuilt the tasks and created applications using MS word, MS Excel
- Contributed to growing the company into top 3 immigration & law firm company in Alberta within 3 years; Supervised projects and team members to boost the business

AVAILABLE LANGUAGES

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Native, Java
- Back-End: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Java, C, GraphQL
- Others: MS Office Software(Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Adobe XD, Linux

PROJECTS

Portfolio Homepage To-do List D-day Calculator Snake Game Drawing Web Application Weather App

CONTACT

L+1 (587) 973 5519

☑kevin.kim9685@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/kevin-jaehan-kim

EDUCATION

Diploma of Information Technology Software Development

South Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT) 2020 - 2021(on-going) Calgary, AB